<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="92">
    <author>Raster R3 Modding</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>BigBags As Default</en>
        <de>BigBags Als Standard</de>
        <fr>BigBags Par Défaut</fr>
        <es>BigBags Por Defecto</es>
    </title>
<description>
<en>
<![CDATA[Do you like Big Bags? Are you used to using them in your games?

With this mod you will no longer have to regret that when you unload your seeders or fertilizers,
and lose your precious BigBags in favor of pallets. Now when unloading seeds, fertilizer, lime,
salt or pig food, by default BigBags will be used. This will affect all vehicles and even factories
that do not specify otherwise.

Enjoy your BigBags and forget about handling annoying pallets...]]>
</en>
<de>
<![CDATA[Magst du Big Bags? Bist du es gewohnt, sie in deinen Spielen zu verwenden?

Mit dieser Mod musst du das nicht mehr bedauern, wenn du deine Sämaschinen oder Dünger ablädst,
und Ihre wertvollen BigBags zugunsten von Paletten verlieren. Jetzt werden beim Entladen von Saatgut, Dünger, Kalk,
Salz oder Schweinefutter werden jetzt standardmäßig BigBags verwendet. Dies betrifft alle Fahrzeuge und sogar Fabriken
die nichts anderes angeben.

Genießt eure BigBags und vergesst das lästige Hantieren mit Paletten...]]>
</de>
<fr>
<![CDATA[Vous aimez les Big Bags ? Avez-vous l'habitude de les utiliser dans vos jeux ?

Avec ce mod vous n'aurez plus à regretter que lorsque vous déchargez vos semoirs ou engrais, vous perdiez votre précieux
BigBags au profit des palettes. Désormais, lors du téléchargement de graines, d'engrais, de chaux, de sel ou d'aliments pour porcs, par défaut
Des BigBags seront utilisés. Cela affectera tous les véhicules et même les usines qui ne précisent pas le contraire.

Profitez de vos BigBags et oubliez la manipulation de palettes ennuyeuses...]]>
</fr>
<es>
<![CDATA[¿Te gustan las BigBags? ¿Estás acostumbrado a usarlas en tus partidas?

Con este mod ya no tendrás que lamentar que al descargar tus sembradoras o abonadoras, pierdas tus preciadas
BigBags en favor de los pallets. Ahora al descargar semillas, abono, cal, sal o comida para cerdos, por defecto
se usarán las BigBags. Esto afectará a todos los vehículos e incluso a las fábricas que no especifiquen lo
contrario.

Disfruta de tus BigBags y olvídate de manejar molestos pallets...]]>
</es>
</description>
	
    <iconFilename>modIcon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
	
	<fillTypes filename="newfilltypes.xml" />
</modDesc>